Hello, you're cute
こんにちわ 可愛いですね
I want to draw how good you look. I'm nervous. Sorry.
似 合いを描きたいですね 緊張してます ごめんなさい、
I suddenly turned the camera around for a moment.
急にカメラを回した ちょっとね、
So cute
可愛くて
Wow, you brought your child. Please check your background. What are you doing now?
すごい 子連れてきましたね 経歴に聞いてやってください 今何
Is it being done?
か されてる?
I'm just an office worker. Did you do anything before?
普通に会社員です 元々何かやってた?
I was an idol after graduating from high school, but I quit.
高校卒業してから アイドルやってたけど 辞めて、
I'm an office worker right now, right? I'm an idol, right?
今会社員です アイドルだろ?
I was an idol, but I quit. Well, I see.
アイドルだったけど辞めちゃった まあそっか、
That's right
そうなんだ
Singing, dancing, performing live, and debuting 2.
歌 って、踊って ライブして、デビューして 2、
3 years?
3年?
You were popular after you graduated from high school, right?
高校卒業してから 人気あったでしょ 本当?
I do live performances and occasionally get the chance, which is amazing. Why should I read it?
ライブとかやって たまに 機会とか すごいな なんで読めちゃ
Did you?
った の?
I'm tired
疲れちゃった
Are you tired?
疲 れちゃった?
I'm really curious, what does it mean?
すごく気になるんですけど どういうの?
Is it a lesson?
レッスンとかですか?
Did something unpleasant happen to you?
いろいろって、もしかして何か嫌なことがあったりしたの?
What you don't like?
嫌なこと?
Dislike
嫌
Where should I go?
れた り どれに?
Like a producer, Zakuhar?
プロデューサーみたいな ザクハル?
Yes, yes, that's right. That's right. People in a privileged position are so-called pillow sales people.
はいはい、そっちね そっか えらい立場の人が いわゆる枕営業
Did he tell you to have sex with me?
俺 とエッチしろよみたいな 言われた?
It looks like it's going to sell, so what did you do?
売れるよみたいな で、何しちゃったの?
I've done it before, but was it a lie?
しちゃったこともある そっか でもなんか嘘だった?
It didn't sell at all, but you really didn't like it, right?
全然売れなかった それはでも本当は嫌だったでしょ?
Yeah, I hated it, but I had a dream, I see.
うん、嫌だったけどね 夢があって そっか、
That was painful, there was a lot of darkness, right?
それ辛かったね いろいろ闇があるんだね はい、
Yes, auntie is working normally now?
ありました え、今おばちゃん普通に働いてる?
Ordinarily, from a long time ago, uh, from a really glamorous world, isn't it?
普通に、昔 えー、なんかすごい華やかな世界から あれだね
What do you say?
どう いう?
What series?
何系?
It's just normal business. Oh, that's right. You hate sales, right? It's cute.
普通の営業です あ、そうなんだ 営業嫌いだよね 可愛いしね
Please don't be fooled by bad people who are friendly.
人 当たりも良い 悪い人に 騙されないように してください
Isn't it popular?
モ テるでしょ?
I'm not popular at all. What about your boyfriend?
全然モテないよ 彼氏は?
I haven't been there for about a year. Did you say it was a year ago?
1年くらいいない 1年前は言ったの?
I dated him for a little while when I was an idol.
ちょっと だけ ちょっとだけ付き合ったよ アイドル時代は 彼
I can't make a name like Mr. I couldn't make one.
氏 とか作れないもんね 作れなかった
Why did you break up with your boyfriend?
彼 氏とはなんで別れたの?
I guess that's right. I guess that's right.
それ そうだろう それそうなんだろうけど あ、
That's right, well, hey, he's an amazing idol producer.
そうなんだ まあ、ちょっと すごいアイドル プロデューサー
Is that true?
とか もやられてる そうなの?
I'm not a bad person, but I graduated as an idol and now I'm at work.
悪い人じゃないんだよ でも アイドルで卒業して 今職場のアイ
Dollars, right?
ド ルでしょ?
I'm not an idol after all
結局アイドルじゃない
These socks leave behind an idol smell, after all, somewhere.
この ソックスが アイドル臭残してるからね や っぱ どこか
I have some regrets, but it feels good.
に 未練はあるよ いい感じ
Not nice clothes
素 敵な服じゃない
Please show me your whole body coordination.
全 身コーディネート ちょっと見せてください
Can't you still go on stage?
今 でもステージいけるんじゃない?
Can I go?
い けますか?
Just like this
ちょっとこうやって
Try spinning around, can't you do it like this?
ク ルっとふわっと 回ってみて こうやってできないの?
I feel curly
クルっとします
It's okay, there are probably fans who like this kind of thing too.
大丈夫、 こういう感じの好きな ファンたちも多分いたんで
Isn't this a hotel? Honestly, the producer told me...
ここ はホテルじゃないですか 正直 プロデューサーから エッ
Ji's invitation came and the producer's sex was good.
チ のお誘い方が来て プロデューサーのエッチって上手だった
of?
の?
I'm really curious, are those people good?
すごい 気になるんだけど あの人たちは上手いの?
It's not good, no one will release this, so go to the producer.
上手くはないよ 誰もこれ公開しないから プロデューサーに向か
Tell me you're bad at sex, Producer.
って エッチ下手だぞって言ってやって プロデューサーエッチ下
It's a hand. The producer is bad at sex. What's his name?
手 だぞ プロデューサーエッチ下手だぞ なんて名前?
People like Matsumoto Matsumoto Matsumoto P I'm not good at sex.This is what I want.
松本さんみたいな人 松本 松本P エッチ下手だぞ これがアイ
It's a dollar. It's scary. It's expensive right now.
ド ルですよ 怖い 今ね 高い
Haven't you had a meeting?
会 見はしてない?
I haven't had a press conference. I'm not sure if there's interest or not.
会見はしてない 興味があるかないかって 興味があるわけ
This, by the way, is that. It's a skirt. It has a guard inside.
これ ちなみにあれだね スカートだね 中にガードのある イ
It's not the one with the skirt. There's no skirt.
ンナ ーのあるスカートじゃないやつだね スカートないんです
Under this, it's underwear.
この 下、下着なんだ
My skin is all a bit messy.
な に肌か全部 ちょっとこっから散らぐらい 散らぐらい こ
It's just a mess
っ から散らぐらいだね
Isn't he sexy?
セ クシーなやつじゃない?
Maybe
もしかして
Is your job selling underwear?
お 仕事なんか下着販売とか?
Like
みたいな
Does it roll up about halfway at the bottom?
下 で半分ぐらいまで まくれたりする?
Until this much?
このぐらいまで?
How about from here to here from the hem?
ここから裾からここぐらい このぐらいはどう?
I think the stage costume had a hem like that, too.
ステージのコスチュームでも そんぐらいの裾あったんじゃない?
one more time
もう 一回
If I had known this around then, I would have bought a lot of instax cars and paid for them.
この 頃に知ってたら 僕はチェキをいっぱい買ってた 課金して
Are you embarrassed?
た 恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing. We don't love each other at all. We both wear skirts.
恥ずかしい まったく愛し合ってない 2人とも スカートどんぐ
Can leprosy be raised?
らい 上げられる?
a little below
ちょっと下
There?
そ こ?
more than this
これ以上
The wind blew The wind blew
風 吹いた 風吹いた
Attacking underwear?
攻 めてる下着?
Maybe it's the underwear I'm attacking.
攻めてる下着かな かもしれない
You look so cute
こんな 可愛い顔して
It's a small area.
面 積少なめだね
When I got here, I stuck my butt out.
ここ まできたらお尻を出しちゃいました
Look at that idol's turn.
あの 顔振る見てて アイドルの振り向き
It's a really low angle, so it's like a photo shoot.
ガ ッチリローアングルだから 撮影会みたいなの ローアングル
flows from
から 流れてくる
That's a nice ass
の いいお尻だね
Do you still play sports or work out?
今 でもスポーツとかやって 鍛えてたりとかするの?
Are you not doing anything?
何もしてないの?
Let's go
行っちゃいましょう
Are you embarrassed?
恥 ずかしいでございますか
What is this yet?
まだ これ何?
Is this a decoration?
これ飾り?
Can I continue like this?
このまま行けるの?
I think I can go.
行けると思うけど
I think I should leave my socks on. It would be embarrassing to leave my socks on.
ソ ックスはね、残しちゃおうかな ソックス残しちゃ恥ずかしく
do not have?
ない?
I have become a boppang girl now
ボ ッパンになった もう
Turn around once
一 回後ろ向いて
As expected, this is because I am tired from my normal company work.
さ すがにこれは普段の会社業務で お疲れの
Those are cute feet.
可愛 い足だね
Try squeezing your foot.Does it hurt next time?
足 グーしてみて 次パー 痛い?
It's here, right?
ここだよね?
Your voice has changed a bit.
ちょっと 声変わってきちゃったね
Does it feel good here?
ここ気持ちいい?
I could see it.
見えちゃいました
That's amazing.
すごいね
My abdominal muscles move a lot just by touching my nipples.
乳首触っているだけで腹筋すごい動くね
Does it feel good here?
ここ気持ちいいの?
I think I'll stop talking about art.
芸のこと喋るのやめようと思います
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
Are you standing like this?
こんなに立っちゃうの?
Isn't it so embarrassing?
すごい恥ずかしくない?
Very top.
すっごく上
These are panties, aren't they too high up?
これパンティーさ、上にあげすぎじゃない?
This is digging into me.
食い込んでるよ、これ
It's amazing, I want to crawl behind it.
なんかすごい、そっから後ろにゾコゾコしたいな
Producer Matsumoto: Did you work standing up?
松本プロデューサー 立ちワークしたの?
did.
した
Did you do it?
したの?
That's right, I'm getting used to this style right away.
そうだよね、すぐにこのスタイルに乗せられてる
hey.
ね
It's amazingly soaked.
すごい ビショビショだね
Does this make you this wet?
これ、こんなに濡れるの?
Seriously, it's fine
まじかよ、結構
...
Yami: I think we might be able to finish some of the behind-the-scenes stuff.
闇 影業的なやつ結構終えるかもなんじゃないの?
Hasn't this happened?
こんなことない?
I'm so wet.
めちゃめちゃ濡れてる
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
It feels good, no doubt.
気持ちいいでしょ、間違いなく
You're putting a lot of pressure into your toes.
つま先にすごい力入っちゃってるでしょ
You're the one who really feels it.
ガチで感じてるやつでしょ
Her pussy is amazing though.
マンコジルがすごいんだけど
Did you hear me?
聞こえてた?
Now.
今の
It's so pink.
めちゃめちゃピンク色だね
copper?
どう?
I was so soaked.
自分こんなにビショビショに濡れてて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Having trouble deciding where to look?
目のやりどころに困る?
目のやりどころに困っちゃう?
Do you want to give it a proper shot?
ちゃんと撃ってみる?
Sit down?
下に座る?
It's hard to know where to look.
目のやりどころに困っちゃうもんね
line of sight height.
視線の高さ
Have you ever touched a penis?
もちんちん触ったことあるよね
Looks like you licked it a little?
ちょっと舐めたそう?
Maybe.
もしかして
That's right, if you've come this far.
そうだよね、ここまで来たらね
I licked it.
舐めちゃったね
Look at your waist.
腰、見てみて
Let's go teach you something.
ちょっと教えに行こう
I feel like I can rest my head here.
ここに頭を乗っける感じ
It feels like I'm stepping on the side.
横に踏んでいる感じ
Kick this leg.
こっちの足を蹴る
That's really cool.
すごいかっこいいね
Don't stand up.
立てないで
Your butt is the best.
お尻が最高なんだよね
Can you talk with this?
これで喋れる?
Fumiko, try touching it yourself.
文子、ちょっと自分で触ってみてよ
Check out what's going on.
どうなってるか実況してみて
Try touching it lightly.
軽く触ってみて
slimy.
ぬるぬる
Is it slimy?
ぬるぬるしてる?
It's really slimy.
本当にぬるぬるしてるね
I can't see all the way to my butt.
お尻まで丸見えない
Is it embarrassing to come this far?
ここまで来ても恥ずかしい?
That butt.
そのお尻
Can I press you from above?
上から押しつかり回っていい?
You pressed it against me.
ぬるぬる押しつけたね
A nice shot.
形のいいショット
Will this come out?
これ出る?
It might have come out.
出ちゃったかも
You tightened it at the end, right?
最後締めたでしょ?
Not tightened?
締めてない?
It felt good though.
気持ちよかったんだけど
Because I'm the type who has an active butt.
お尻が活発するタイプだから
Look, it's okay now.
ほ ら、もう大丈夫
Can I continue?
続きしていい?
Does that mean you're okay?
大丈夫ってこと?
It hurts a bit
ちょっと痛いで
Sho.
しょ
That's amazing.
すごい ね
You're saying something absurd.
無茶苦茶言ってるね
Shall we try moving?
動いてみる?
Try moving
動 いてみ
hand.
て
How do you move?
ど んな動き方するの?
What, you made me move like that?
何、そうやって動いてあげたの?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Is it correct?
当たってるの?
What's in this?
これ何が入ってますか?
what?
何ですか?
What's in this?
これ何が入ってるんですか?
Try saying it.
言ってみて
Do you want me to say it?
言わせたいの?
What is this?
これ何ですか?
Are you too embarrassed to say it?
恥ずかしくて言えない?
Did it come out?
出ちゃった?
What do you say?
何言うの?
what are you doing?
何してるの?
I'm taking a bath.
お風呂入ってますよ
I spent a lot of time there.
いっぱいいちしてたもんね
tired.
疲れた
tired?
疲れた?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
Excuse me while I take a bath.
入浴中すみません
Well then, this way.
じゃあ、こっち
I was squishing in the water.
水の中でシュコシュコしてた
It feels kind of naughty.
なんかやらしい感じになってる
While looking at me.
こっち見ながら
You're going to die.
死ぬんですね
You're not going to die at all.
全然死ぬんじゃないよ
I'm not going to die.
死ぬんじゃないよ
What are you talking about?
何言ってるんですか?
If I didn't die, I wouldn't be depressed.
死なかったら落ちんじん立ってないよ
I want you to do more terrorist attacks.
もういっぱいテロテロしてほしいよ
We talked a lot.
いっぱい喋られちゃった
Give me a little something back.
ちょっとお返しを
Give something back.
お返しを
お 返 し を
Can't you handle the role?
役のことできんのかな?
It rained a little.
ちょっと降って降っちゃった
Can you go?
いける?
Do you think you can go?
いけると思う?
Come up.
上がってよ
You're getting wet.
濡れちゃってるじゃん
Can you touch the shadow of the moon?
月の影に手ついてもらえ?
I think it's going to fall like this.
このままズボッと落ちちゃうと思うけど
You're reacting really well.
めちゃめちゃいい反応してるじゃん
Is it okay if I say I want to wash my face in anger?
怒り洗面欲しいってことでいいの?
Let's go with that outfit.
その格好のままで行ってみよう
Just a little lick and this...
ちょっと舐めただけでこれとか...
Something like this...
これとか...
Was it a motivation switch that you just licked?
今舐めたのやる気スイッチだった?
Was it a motivation switch?
やる気スイッチだった?
Did you just sneak away?
今ちょっとこそっていっちゃった?
It happened.
なっちゃったね
My hair is now the same as when I was born.
生まれたての腰髪になっちゃってる